Guide to the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of Thomas Applequist as dean, circa 1983-2005; Accession 2019-A-0028
  - Department Chair files
    - Renaissance Studies, 1990-1998 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Slavic Studies, 1989-1997 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Social Thought and Ethics, 1992-1994 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Sociology, 1992-1998 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Soviet and East European Studies, 1990-1994 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Spanish and Portuguese, 1990-1998 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Statistics, 1990-1998 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Western European Studies, 1990-1993 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Whitney Humanities Center, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Women's Studies, 1990-1993 (Box 9, Folder 16)